Guide to the Urie Bronfenbrenner papers, [ca. 1960-2011]
Bronfenbrenner, Urie papers, [ca. 1960-2011]
- Series IV. Correspondence Files
  - Lambert, Wallace, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Landers, Ann (Eppie Lederer), 1980-1987 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Laosa, Luis, 1983-1991 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Lazar, Irving, 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Lee, Phillip, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Lempert, Wolfgang, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Lerner, Richard, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - Levenstein, Phyllis, 1973-1977 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Levin, Iris, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - LeVine, Bob, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - Lewin, Miriam, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Hara, Hiroko, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Liegle, Ludwig, 1974-1988 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Light, Richard, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Lipsitt, Lewis P., 1982 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Luscher, Kurt, 1976-1988 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Luscher, Kurt, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - Luster, Tom, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 46)
  - Luster, Tom, 1989-1994 (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Luthar, Sumiya, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Macoby, Eleanor, 1982-1990 (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Madison, Joe, 1984-1986 (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - Magnusson, David, 1982-1997 (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - Mahoney, Maureen, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - Malaguzzi, Loris, 1986-1989 (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - Malewska, Hanna E., 1969 (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - Maples, Mary, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - Marcus, Joseph, 1969-1975 (Box 19, Folder 64)
  - Matsuda, Sei, 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - McAdoo, Harriette, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 66)
  - McCall, Robert, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 67)
  - McHugh, Matt, 1975-1988 (Box 19, Folder 68)
  - Meili, Richard, 1961-1982 (Box 19, Folder 69)
  - Merrow, John, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 70)
  - Miles, Margaret (Box 19, Folder 71)
  - Miyake, Kazuo, 1981-1983 (Box 19, Folder 72)
  - Mohatt, Gerald, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 73)
  - Montado, Leo, 1977-1985 (Box 19, Folder 74)
  - Montagu, Ashley, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 75)
  - Moore, Evelyn, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 76)
  - Moore, Raymond, 1973-1975 (Box 19, Folder 77)
  - Moore, Pickens, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 78)
  - Morris, Pamela, 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 79)
  - Morse, Bill, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 80)
  - Moynihan, Senator Daniel P. (Statements also), 1985-1989 (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - Muenster, 1980-1984 (Box 19, Folder 81)
  - Muus, Rolf, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 82)
  - Nathan, Henry, 1974-1976 (Box 19, Folder 83)
  - Neville, Peter, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 48)
  - Nichols, Bruce (Box 26, Folder 49)
  - Nicolopoulou, Ageliki, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 84)
  - Nightengale, Narina, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 85)
  - Norton, Arthur, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 86)
  - Oerter, Rolf, 1981-1984 (Box 19, Folder 87)
  - Oh, Moonia, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 88)
  - Ooms, Theodora, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 50)
  - Orrange, Robert, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 51)
  - Perkins, James A., 1992 (Box 19, Folder 89)
  - Piel, Gerard, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 90)
  - Pulkkinen, Lea, 1982-1988 (Box 19, Folder 91)
  - Pusateri, Catherine, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 52)
  - Pushkin (Box 19, Folder 92)
  - Quie, Albert, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 93)
  - Radin, Norma, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 94)
  - Raspberry, William (Articles also), 1991 (Box 26, Folder 53)
  - Rauh, Hellgaud, 1988-1996 (Box 19, Folder 95)
  - Rede, Roald Hoffmans, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 96)
  - Reykowski, Janusz, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 97)
  - Rhodes, Frank, 1983-1987 (Box 19, Folder 98)
  - Richardson, Barbara, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 99)
  - Richardson, Stephen, 1982-1989 (Box 19, Folder 100)
  - Richmond, Julius, 1987-1989 (Box 19, Folder 101)
  - Riley, Dave, 1983-1987 (Box 19, Folder 102)
  - Robinson, Halbert, 1972-1974 (Box 19, Folder 103)
  - Robinson, Jo Ann, 1990-1993 (Box 19, Folder 104)
  - Rogers, Lisa, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 105)
  - Rogers, Ruth, 1979-1985 (Box 19, Folder 106)
  - Rogoff, Barbara, 1993-1995 (Box 19, Folder 107)
  - Rosenthal, Gary M., 1997 (Box 19, Folder 108)
  - Rosewater, Ann, 1984-1990 (Box 19, Folder 109)
  - Rowe, Mary P., 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 110)
  - Ruoff, Arthur L., 1994 (Box 19, Folder 111)
  - Ruopp, Dick, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 112)
  - Rutter, Michael, 1982-1988 (Box 19, Folder 113)
  - Savin-Williams, Rich, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 114)
  - Sava, Sam, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 115)
  - Scarr-Salapatek, Sandra, 1972-1989 (Box 19, Folder 116)
  - Schaffer, H. Rudolph, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 54)
  - Scheur, Congressman James, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 117)
  - Schneewind, Klaus A., 1975-1983 (Box 19, Folder 118)
  - Schoggen, Phil, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 120)
  - Schorr, Lisbeth, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 121)
  - Schroeder, Pat, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 122)
  - Schwendler, Wolfgang, 1981-1995 (Box 19, Folder 123)
  - Seaver, W. Burleigh, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 124)
  - Seginer, Rachel, 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 125)
  - Shaffer, Harry, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 126)
  - Shanker, Albert, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 127)
  - Sharp, Laurie, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 128)
  - Sharabani, Ruthie, 1969-1985 (Box 19, Folder 129)
  - Shoho, Alan R., 1998 (Box 26, Folder 55)
  - Shouval, Ron, 1972-1986 (Box 19, Folder 130)
  - Shriver, Eunice and Sargent, 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 131)
  - Shulman, Colette, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 132)
  - Silbereisen, Rainer K., 1983-2000 (Box 19, Folder 133)
  - Silcock, Anne, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 134)
  - Simon, Herbert, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 135)
  - Skinner, Ellen, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 136)
  - Sloutsky, V., 1993 (Box 19, Folder 137)
  - Smith, Brewster, 1986-1988 (Box 19, Folder 138)
  - Sroufe, L. Alan, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 56)
  - Staffanson, Elisabeth, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 139)
  - Steinberg, Laurence, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 57)
  - Steinberg, Lawrence, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 140)
  - Stetsenko, Anna, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 141)
  - Storo, Jan, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 142)
  - Streissguth, Ann, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 143)
  - Striner, Herbert E., 1969 (Box 19, Folder 144)
  - Sugarman, Julie, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 145)
  - Thompson, Ross, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 146)
  - Titus, Jim, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 147)
  - Tizard, Jack, 1976-1978 (Box 19, Folder 148)
  - Trause, Mary Anne, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 149)
  - Tudge, Jon, 1982-1987 (Box 19, Folder 150)
  - Tuttle, William M., 1991 (Box 19, Folder 151)
  - Tyszkowa, Maria, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 152)
  - Ulrich, Robert, 1971-1977 (Box 19, Folder 153)
  - U.S. Government Officials, 1961-1989 (Box 26, Folder 58)
  - Vasta, Ross, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 59)
  - Vygotsky (Box 19, Folder 154)
  - Wachs, Ted, 1990-1998 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Wakai, Kunio, 1983-1995 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Wandersman, Lois Pall, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Watts, Harold, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Weisz, John, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Wertsch, James, 1983-1988 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Wertsch, James, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 60)
  - Wheeler, Mary Ebel, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - White, Sheldon, 1974-1995 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - White, Tara, 1994-1995 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Williams, Lawrence K., 1970 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Williams, Robin M., Jr., 1985 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Willis, Marilyn, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Wolins, Martin, 1972-1981 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Woodward, Ken, 1976-1980 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Wynne, Edward, 1977-1984 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Yarrow, Peter, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Zaporoshetz, A. V., 1976-1985 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Ziegler, Jerome, 1986-1996 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Zigler, Edward F.: A, 1973-1995 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Zigler, Edward F.: B, 1973-1995 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1988-2001 (Box 26, Folder 61)
  - Comments by Colleagues on Drafts, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 62)
  - Correspondence honoring Urie's Retirement, 1987 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence honoring Urie's Retirement, 1987 (Box 29)
  - Important letters, 1962-1997 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1948-1969 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1970-2006 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, articles with Marianne Riksen-Walraven, 1992-2000 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Postcards sent to Urie, 1960-1969 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Diary of trip to China, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 17)
- Series V. Researcher Files
  - Darling and Steinberg, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Baumrind, 1989-1992 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Contexts of Childrearing, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Darling, Nancy, 1994-1995 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Patterns of Childrearing: Gibbs, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Mother and Metalpelet (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Patterns of Childrearing: Steinberg, 1989-1990 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Patterns of Authority (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Socialization and Social Class Through Time and Space (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Parental Beliefs: Palacios, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Children's Social Networks: Feiring, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Social Networks: Robins, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Father Absence, 1959-1982 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Play: Cole, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Peer Influences: Subbotskii (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Mother-Child: Conger, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Carlson, Warren J., 1984 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Mother-Child: Bugental and Shenum, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Strange Situations: Macoby, 1971-1973 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Scarr: Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Patterson, 1987-1991 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Intelligence: Clarke and Clarke, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Preschool Interventions: Levenstein, 1988-1992 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Research Foundation, 1986-1989 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Head Start: Chalkey, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Cover Letter to "Moral Dilemma Experiment" Research Packet (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Instructions for Assistants (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - F-3995 Script and Directions (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Title unknown (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Sample Chart for Use in Dilemma Experiment (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - F-3997X "The Nice Hat" (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - F-3997 Y "The Halloween Prank" (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - F-3997 Z "The Babysitter" (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - F-5018 "Peer Condition As Second Condition" (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - F-5019 Adult Condition as Second Condition (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - Dilemma Experiments: Notes on Analysis Procedure (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - Dilemma Means Tables, 1972-1975 (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - Instrument Paper Current, 1975-1976 (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - F-3994 Research Notes for Administrator (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - Questionaire Blanks for Ithaca, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - PPMT Reliability/CSAI Description (Box 20, Folder 61)
  - Parent Behavior Questionnaire, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 62)
  - Cornell Socialization Agent Inventory: Instrument Paper, 1966-1976 (Box 20, Folder 63)
  - E-4364 A (Box 20, Folder 64)
  - E-4364 A Example: "The Late TV Show" (Box 20, Folder 65)
  - Instructions for Blue Answer Sheet and Part 1 of The Questionnaire (Box 20, Folder 66)
  - Green Booklet: Series of Statements, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 67)
  - Daycare Questionnaire: Memorial University of Newfoundland (Box 20, Folder 68)
  - Instructions for Activities Checklist (Box 20, Folder 69)
  - Prospect and Retrospect, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 70)
  - Activity Profile, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 71)
  - Interviewer's Instructions for Selecting Salient Activities, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 72)
  - Family Background Questionnaire (Box 20, Folder 73)
  - Joint Activities Checklist (Box 20, Folder 74)
  - "People in my Life", 1985 (Box 20, Folder 75)
  - Activities Checklist, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 76)
  - Activity Profile, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 77)
  - Getting Started, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 78)
  - Instrumental (Box 20, Folder 79)
  - Instructions for Administering of Questionnaires (Box 20, Folder 80)
  - Family Life Inventory (Box 20, Folder 81)
  - Part II: Parents in the Home (Box 20, Folder 82)
  - Future Hopes and Plans (Box 20, Folder 83)
  - Some Questions Form Z(a) (b) (Box 20, Folder 84)
  - Criteria for Common Learning, 1983-1987 (Box 20, Folder 85)
  - Common Learning Correspondence, 1983-1987 (Box 20, Folder 86)
  - Commission Membership, 1984-1988 (Box 20, Folder 87)
  - Common Learning Commission Meetings/Minutes, 1983-1988 (Box 20, Folder 88)
  - Common Learning: Financial, 1982-1986 (Box 20, Folder 89)
  - Katie Gottschalk, 1983-1985 (Box 20, Folder 90)
  - Peter McClelland, 1983-1987 (Box 20, Folder 91)
  - Information on Common Learning, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 92)
  - Newspaper Articles: Common Learning (Box 20, Folder 93)
  - College of Human Ecology, 1981-1989 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Common Learning Course Proposals A, 1983-1988 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Common Learning Course Proposals B., 1983-1988 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Johnson Foundation, 1972-1976 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Child Reach, 1990-1991 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - The French American Foundation, 1990-1991 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Advisory Committee on Services for Families with Infants and Toddlers (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Family Matters, 1990-1999 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Divorce: Hetherington, 1970-1979 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Cold War and Class War: Weston, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Single Parent: Michelson, 1980-1982 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Remarriage and Stepparenthood, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Infant Temperament: Stability and Sequelae, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Temperament: Lerner, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Change and Continuity In Infancy: Kagan, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Interacting Systems of Human Development (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Review of Life Course Institute, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Ecology of Alcohol in Pregnancy, 1983-7 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Alcohol in Pregnancy: Streissguth (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Smoking-Prenatal: Naeye, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Birth Order: Anxiety (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Mother-Neonate: Kaye, 1974, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Mother-Newborn: Lamb and Malkin, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Sex Differences: Mother-Neonate Interaction: Moss (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Neonatal Effects of Birth Order: Bell, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Korner, Anneliese, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Belsky: Reproductive Strategy, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Sex Differences: Parent-Infant Interaction, 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - First Year: Fathers: Kotelchuk, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Mother-Infant: Bronson, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Bornstein, 1991-3 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Mother-Infant Separation, 1960-1979 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Attachment: Aber, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Attachment: Sroufe, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Crockenberg: Social Supports, 1984-92 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Feiring, Candace, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Mother-Infant: Trevarthen, 1989-1992 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Papousek, Hanus, 1982-1991 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Mother-Infant: Dunhan, 1990-1994 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Infancy: Rutter, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Sibling System: Dunn, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Infancy - Sibling Systems: Voss, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Physical Environment: Wachs, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Alternative Perspectives: Wachs, 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Father - Infant: Lamb correspondence, 1977-1984 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Children in the World of Work, 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Youth Employment: Mortimer, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Steinberg et al, 1984-1986 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Transition to Work: Greenberger and Steinberg, 1981-1984 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Puberty - Girls: Brooks and Dunn, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Adolescents and Family: Dornbusch, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Adolescence and Parenthood: Selman, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - Magnusson, David, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Youth Organizations, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - Single Parenthood: Dornbusch, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - Morsbach, Helmut, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - Clausen, John, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - Clarke, Alan and Ann, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - Social Networks: Cochran and Bo, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - Sibereisen, Rainer, 1986-1988 (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - Teenage Pregnancy: Furstenburg, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - Adolescent Parenthood: Lamb, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 62)
  - Assortative Mating: Caspi, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 63)
  - Scarr: Rebuttal, 1991-1993 (Box 21, Folder 64)
  - New/Old Commentary, 1992-1993 (Box 21, Folder 65)
  - Nature-Nurture Reconceptualized, 1992-1993 (Box 21, Folder 66)
  - Vandenberg, Steven, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 67)
  - Emlen, Stephen, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 68)
  - Genetics: Gottleib, 1993-1994 (Box 21, Folder 69)
  - Robinson, Jo Ann, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 70)
  - Simonton, Dean Keith, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 71)
  - Scarr: Current, 1990-1 (Box 21, Folder 72)
  - Scarr: Constructing Psychology, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 73)
  - Behavioral Genetics: Lerner, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 74)
  - Plomin: Genetics of Environment, 1983-1990 (Box 21, Folder 75)
  - Stein, Zena: Dutch Famine, 1972-1974 (Box 21, Folder 76)
  - Twins: Infancy - Freedman, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 77)
  - Plomin: primary, 1982-1984 (Box 21, Folder 78)
  - Plomin Correspondence: Secondary, 1983-4 (Box 21, Folder 79)
  - Infancy: Organism Environment Interaction - Wilson & Matheny, 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 80)
  - Matheny, Adam P., 1982-1984 (Box 21, Folder 81)
  - Genetics - Environment Interactions: Primary, 1960-1973 (Box 21, Folder 82)
  - Norway, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 83)
  - Germany, 1998-1999 (Box 21, Folder 84)
  - Israel Road for Peace, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 85)
  - Belsky, Jay, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 86)
  - Day Care: Melhuish, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 87)
  - McCartney, Kathleen, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 88)
  - Heber, Rick, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 89)
  - Egypt Project: Wachs, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 90)
  - Series III: Researchers
  - Day Care: Kagan, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Day Care: Blehar, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Small, Steve, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Luster, Tom, 1991-1992 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Alaska, 1985-1991 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Dornbusch, Sanford, 1990-1993 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Germany, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Head Start Planning Committee, 1965-1997 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Bell, Terrel H., 1975 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Brademas, John, 1969-1978 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Regents Medal of Excellence, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Bayh, Birch, 1961-1978 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Mondale, Walter, 1971-1984 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Institution of International Education: Convocation, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Kurt Lewin Award Release, 1977-1980 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Massachusetts Governor's Committee, 1976-1983 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - White House Conference Address, 1978-1980 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Mondale/Califano, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Committee Hearings, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - National Advisory Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Hearings Committee on Ways and Means 91st Congress, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Conable, Barber B., 1982 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Legislation, 1969-1971 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Child Development Act, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Congressional Testimony, 1973-09-25 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Washington Post, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - ISSBD, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Social Class Through Time, Space and Science, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Grant Foundation Talk, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Regents Medal of Excellence, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Bayh, Birch, 1961-1978 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Mondale, Walter, 1971-84 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Institution of International Education: Convocation, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Kurt Lewin Award Release, 1977-80 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - MA Governor's Committee, 1976-1983 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - White House Conference Address, 1978-1980 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Mondale/Califano, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Committee Hearings, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - National Advisory Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Hearings Committee on Ways and Means 91st Congress, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Conable, Barber B., 1982 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Legislation, 1969-1971 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Child Development Act, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Congressional Testimony, 1973-09-25 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Washington Post, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - ISSBD, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Social Class Through Time, Space and Science, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Grant Foundation Talk, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Lectures in USSR (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Misrep. Statement Congressional Record Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - U.S. Medical Ecology Mission, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Character Development in USA/Soviet Union, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Soviet Field Notes, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - USSR: Miscellaneous Articles, 1960-1969 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - The Changing Soviet Family (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - How the Russians Build Character: Notes (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Report: Making of the New Soviet Man, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Upbringing in Collective Setting in Switzerland and USSR (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Makarenko and the Collective Family, 1966-7 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Informing on Associates (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Institutional Approaches to Cultural Deprivation: American and Soviet, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Psychological Bases of Soviet Secrecy (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Some Possible Effects of a Large-Scale Shelter Program (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - "A New Approach", 1961 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Introduction to Soviet Manual, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Soviet Views of America at War (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - USSR: Teacher's Journal on Delegation, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Contemporary Trends in Soviet Society, 1960-? (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - School Effectiveness in Ecological Perspective, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Human Development and Public Policy: SRCD, June 1984 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Who Cares for Our Children?, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - New York Times Article, 1988-02-15 (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - University of South Carolina Commencement, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - Carnegie Mellon Address, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - University of North Carolina, 1989-04 (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - Yale University, 1994-02 (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - University of California Berkeley, February 1992 (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - McGill University, March 1995 (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - Society for the Investigation of Human Ecology, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - International Research and Exchange Board (Box 22, Folder 61)
  - Chinese Paradox (Box 22, Folder 62)
  - "Inner Conflict and Defense": Miller and Swanson (Box 22, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence: Bednarski and Araujo (Box 22, Folder 64)
  - Hawaii Case, 1996-7 (Box 22, Folder 65)
  - Goteborgs-Zurich, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 66)
  - The Shelter-Centered Society: Letter to the Editor (Box 22, Folder 67)
  - American Family: Trends and Pressures, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 68)
  - Dobbs, Bettina, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 69)
  - Twins: Akerman and Fischbein, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 70)
  - Baker Gala, 1988-04-30 (Box 22, Folder 71)
  - Human Development in Context, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 72)
  - Bibliography: Middle Childhood (Box 22, Folder 73)
  - Family-School-Person: Epstein, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 74)
  - I.Q. in Black and White, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 75)
  - Curriculum for Caring, 1977-1984 (Box 22, Folder 76)
  - Educational Testing Service: Primary, 1990-1991 (Box 22, Folder 77)
  - Social Effects of Ability Grouping, 1966-1967 (Box 22, Folder 78)
  - Youth Development: Seginer, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 79)
  - Burgess, Robert, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 80)
  - Bruun, Geoffrey, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 81)
  - Evolution of Environment: History (Box 22, Folder 82)
  - Evolution of Environment: Berlin Survey (Box 22, Folder 83)
  - Friendship: Sharabany, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 84)
  - Peer Groups: Kindermann, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 85)
  - Intervention: Home Start, 1971-1973 (Box 22, Folder 86)
  - Perspectives: Shep White, 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 87)
  - Complementary Perspectives: Magnusson, 1989-1993 (Box 22, Folder 88)
  - Children and Families, 1981-1984 (Box 22, Folder 89)
  - Family Size (Box 22, Folder 90)
  - Chase-Landsdale, Lindsay, 1988-9 (Box 23, Folder 1)